import 'package:sight_reading_app/lessons_and_quizzes/question_list.dart';

/// List of questions for lesson 2.
///
/// Teaches how to read F G on Treble clef.

final QuestionList lessonTwoQuestions =
    QuestionList(lessonID: 2, questionList: [
  ///Tutorial
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'F4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question:
  //       'This lesson will teach you 2 more notes. This note is call F (Fa). It is between the 2 lowest lines of the staff. Now press F in the option box.',
  //   correctAnswer: 'F',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'G4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question:
  //       'This note is call G (Sol). The circle is on the second from lowest line of the staff. Now press G in the option box.',
  //   correctAnswer: 'G',
  // ),
  //
  // ///Lesson questions
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'G4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question:
  //       'Try answer these questions on your own with a combination of the previous notes.',
  //   correctAnswer: 'G',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'F4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'F',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'G4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'G',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'E4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'E',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'D4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'D',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'F4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'F',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'C4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'C',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'E4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'E',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'F4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'F',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'G4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'G',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'F4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'F',
  // ),
  // Question(
  //   note: Note(name: 'G4', duration: 4),
  //   clef: Clef.treble,
  //   question: 'What note is this?',
  //   correctAnswer: 'G',
  // ),
]);
